I love that he clocked out right as they
made it a law.
That's funny cuz you know that you're
about to you're about to get arrested if
you don't pay child support. He goes,
"Am I?"
He goes,
"Trish, what if I told you I'm a ticking
time bomb?"
He goes, "I Dan's about to be a
sophomore in high school.
I can't afford that kind of scratch."
He goes, "I'm clocking out. I don't want
to see I don't want to see these what
these midterms are about to do to
Clinton."
He goes, "I'm gone."
I ain't buying a graduation cap for that
big head.
I love you think that Gary would pay
child support.
No, my mom had to garnish eventually.
Me, too. Dude, I love that both Trish
and Terry both went the garnishment
route.
garnished. Did your mom bring it to you
first or she just garnished?
Dude, my mom my mom said it like she
whipped one on him. She goes,
"By the way, I'm garnishing your
father's wages." is what she said.
said it to me and I was so
spun around and just groomed that
I was like, "No, don't do that." I go,
"He told me he has a very high furniture
bill." So, I was using furniture. My
mom's like, "We All of our furniture has
rips in it."
Yeah.
And I'm like, "I know, but he's got nice
stuff. He's really relaxed. He's just
cool. He's so much funnier than you."
Dude, though, I mean, yeah, come on,
he's fun. Dude, my dad would own my mom
when I was little cuz he would Whenever
I'd visit him do you find Dude, we
just we after we were at Dan's Liquors
when we'd put in like probably once a
week at least. I'd spend 6 weeks out
there. Once a week
after our shift at Dan's Liquors
It wasn't your shift, Dan.
I worked the shift.
You didn't work the shift.
I worked the whole shift.
You go in the back and play with guys
and hope no one sees you look at the
porn.
I'd play with my guys on the side of the
counter in the front eating Kit Kats,
drinking Pepsis.
You should be embarrassed.
And then going and playing the arcade
for five bucks, which is pretty badass.
It's pretty good. Everything's
Everything It's a quarter then or were
they 50 cents at that point?
Quarter. Street Fighter 2 just came out.
And Mortal Kombat just came out. It was
great summer.
kids.
I'm a good You're a good kid. But then
we My dad would just take us to Toy
World.
Yeah.
It wasn't us. He would just take me. He
would go by himself.
himself also?
Dude, my dad would buy he bought
Starting Lineups one time when he was
like I was like, "Are those for you?"
And he's like, "Yeah." And I still got
jealous.
trying to hit on the girl with the cans
over on aisle four.
Always slinging it.
Yeah.
And when he lived in Denver still, we
used to go to this bar called
Caldonia's,
which is
Why did you go there?
Cuz my dad wanted to get hammered and it
was my weekend with him.
You were a child.
Yeah.
You weren't supposed to be in there.
They had a video game. They had
Castlevania.
Wait, do you think that was for you?
It was. It was for you.
I mean, it was there was another video
game. Who else was playing?
other children waiting to play the game?
No, there wasn't.
wasn't, Dan. There wasn't, was there?
Yeah, I got
You know why? Cuz it's not for children.
I got to play it. Yeah, now that I think
about
your dad may have brought in that
Castlevania game to occupy you so he can
get hammered with his friends. So he
gets twisted up and then gets
Hey, get out of here, you son of a
We would walk First off, we'd walk my
dad's apartment complex.
had DUIs.
If you're If you're If you're wondering
if you live in Denver, you know this is.
My dad lived on the corner of Iliff and
Parker. There's an apartment complex
down there. And that's right where
Caldonia's was and a gas station called
the Barn Store. My dad and I would walk
across the street
We walk across the street to the Barn
Store, which is like a gas station. He'd
give me some candy for when we went
home. And then we'd go to Caldonia's and
I would I get to eat the candy playing
video games and then my dad would just
get hammered.
Damn.
Yeah, but my dad uh Dude, this you're
going to love this.
the way, is there also bikini girls
there, Dan?
Uh
Your father's not a good guy to you,
huh?
Uh no, he wasn't.
Go back to that original thing. Go back.
Uh they I mean, they did it at night.
Is that Caldonia's right there? Was that
happening?
Dan?
I I wish.
What in the Christ? Dan.
I didn't see that lady there.
Of course you did. That's where your dad
was while you were playing Castlevania.
in the parking lot. I know that Yamaha
store is still there. So that's
definitely still Yeah, dude. This is
where my dad would take me.
What That's That's it. Caldonia's. Dude,
I
want a Caldonias shirt.
smoking breasts is their sign.
Get the double entendre.
They closed. They got knocked down. It's
not there anymore.
This is a couple years ago. It got
closed down, but they uh
my dad and I were walking through the
parking lot. This is a real I was maybe
6 years old. We're walking through the
parking lot and
is a pig smoking a cigarette.
And it says we have smoking breasts.
Somebody went up and put in the words we
have smoking breasts.
gone but not forgotten. I used to uh we
were so we're walking through the
parking lot in the car. I run in front
of my dad and a car stops, you know,
like honks. And I'm in the front. My
dad's like, "Hey!" Like gets in front of
me and puts his hand up. You know, then
we like walk in. I go and play video
games and I come back and my dad is
drinking a beer with the dude that
almost hit me.
That's hilarious. And one of the
girls with a bikini contest sitting on
his lap?
No, there wasn't there
Would you like this to be your new mom,
Danny? I'm just around. Would
you need another dollar for the game?
Here you go.
That was really it though.
That last part was pretty awkward.
Would you need another dollar for the
game? Here you go.
Here you go, bud.
I bothered Trish and Gary at a lot of
bars.
I'm going to get That's bizarre
they used to just bring you to a bunch
of bars.
Yeah. I don't know, man. It's you know.
You were abused.
Wasn't abused.
Dan.
What?
You're not supposed to be in a bar as a
child.
I'm sorry that I have an adult-like
personality cuz I grew up in
Is that how it was? cut to Dan
being a little kid and he's like, "Sing
us a song, you piano man."
Hey bartender, over there. You haven't
her in 5 years. Guys, I'm going
to play Castlevania. Can I get another
Shirley Temple?
And god damn it, step on it. Gary, do a
shot. WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
YEAH.
Saturday night main event's coming on.
We got to go home. I want to watch Hogan
versus Slaughter.
Was he taking you there to get day drunk
or night drunk?
Yeah, both.
Dude, my dad checked out at 48 of
cirrhosis. put in work.
Yeah, dude, my dad uh I didn't realize
to
the bars crazy.
Dude, both my parents took me to bars.
Is that you, DJ Lou?
My mom didn't take me to bars a lot.
She's done it only a couple times. So,
you know.
Did the law get involved?
No, no, no. Gary was like exclusively He
would take me to shifts when he was a
bartender at a bowling alley.
Well, here's the thing.
But, I go bowling.
Oh.
Play. Yeah.
There's things to do there. There's an
arcade usually.
Yeah, there was an arcade.
And there's uh you could eat Otis
Spunkmeyer cookies.
Otis Spunkmeyer cookies.
dude? Who the doesn't? By the way,
walking around these halls, there's an
Otis Spunkmeyer oven in these halls of
serious action.
And I don't know what it's doing. It's
It's not cooked up or nothing.
Yeah.
But, I don't know. Are there other bar
kids out there? 844-99. If you went to a
bar kid If you were a bar kid, cuz it is
weird. I don't
It's real weird.
I don't think My mom's house was like My
mom That was on very rare occasion. I'm
saying like I had a normal life with my
mom.
Any occasion's pretty weird.
But, when I was with my dad, it was
straight-up lawlessness a lot of the
time.
I'm talking about Caledonia's. That's
right after my parents got divorced. So,
my dad's not truly in the gutter yet.
Right.
When he moved to Lake County is when he
went in the gutter. When I'm talking
backwoods, trailer parks, like
Caledonia's pretty bad place to bring a
kid.
Caledonia's I swear to god, probably
just cuz I'm conditioned, but talking
about Lake County versus The places I
went in Lake County versus Caledonia's,
Caledonia's is like awesome. Like you go
to a Hooters maybe. Yeah, it's like the
best memories of me thinking about being
at Caledonia's playing Castle
the Double Deuce? There's
No, it it was always Lakeside. It was
always the the bowling alley in Lakeport
that
we would
That was a rough scene over there,
though.
That was not that bad. I saw some rough
in that bar, though. I saw
people where I was like, "Yo, that
dude's life is" I was like 10.
I was going to say, they all look like
that when you're 10, dude.
in your 10 with Late Night bar people.
But, also my dad was funny.
to I'm going to Robin Williams
you. I'm going to Goodwill Hunting you
in this cuz you're not realizing it and
everyone else in the room is not saying
it.
What?
That's insane that you were hanging out
in bars at 10 years old that much.
Yeah, I mean it was a lot.
It's bananas.
Yeah.
I had some of my best memories of my dad
growing up are hanging out in the
garage. All right, hanging out in the
garage because we would hang out in the
garage, we would listen to music, we
would like shoot BB guns and just chill
out. He was pretty much blackout drunk
the whole time.
see how stupid that sounds?
Sounds pretty great.
But it was great. Like I loved it. I I
loved my childhood.
BB guns sound awesome.
I get it. Trish always made me do work.
If I was at her house, she'd be like,
"Hey, can you weed?" Weed the yard, too.
Weed on the side. Weed on the side of
the house.
Christine and her dad were way better
drinking. They were awesome to hang
with. They were way better hang. Gary
was a fun hang.
A memory of hanging out at Caledonia's
with your dad there. The fact of the
matter, and I know you can say this,
too. Like my goddamn childhood is so
dark and there's so much bad
in it that if I can't remember the
good times of like hanging out and
shooting a BB gun, there's literally
nothing.
I'm serious. I'm serious when I say
that.
Yeah.
cuz everybody was drunk and
But I want a Caledonia shirt. Like I
want to I'm going to find a Caledonia.
I'm going to Oh, yeah. I'm going to have
Bobby make one at Gas Digital cuz it's
like it just uh it's just a funny thing
from my past. Do you know what I mean?
When you grow up and you kind of look
back and you're like, "Oh, it's funny."
I'd rather celebrate that than be what
bummed out by it.
Yeah, I feel like that was horrible. My
dad's a horrible person. It's like,
"Well, everybody's
Oh, you got a bunch of calls?
Bunch of bar children?
Is it Gary?
Did he fake his death 21 years ago? God
damn it.
Man, I didn't know you were on the
radio, bud.
And he goes, "No, come on, man. I mean,
you know, I liked your Comedy Central
hour, your Netflix. I thought it was
kind of a step back, but you know, This
Is Not Happening was great and The
Bonfire.
Holy
Um wow. It's going big. Let's uh let's
throw a random one here. We'll go with
A lot of bar kids.
A lot of bar kids listen to The Bonfire.
Yeah. Big up to all the kids out there.
Christine, you weren't even a bar kid,
you were a garage kid.
Yeah, any garage kids with crippled
mothers.
Oh man, that's a different that's a
different uh
It's a different kind of love.
It's a different branch in the same
army.
Yeah.
Um
this is the kid army.
You're the navy, I'm the air force.
Maria, Chicago Chicago.
Oh, you must be hanging out in some fun
Chicago bars.
Maria, you there?
I only went to one. Yeah.
Only one, home of the Malort shot?
No, my grandfather was Polish and he
went across the street to the from the
church and would bring me with that like
6 years old.
Yeah.
And I would play pinball and pool.
That's how I learned how to play pool.
And by the way, you know how much second
hand smoke you and I were both exposed
to at 6 years old? That's when you
smoked in bars. You smoked in You smoked
a lot in bars.
Uh
Uh I have asthma because of it now.
Really?
That's hilarious. We'll smoke anything
at Caledonia's. There's your nice shirt
for you.
Yeah, dude, I'm going to get a
Caledonia's shirt. Believe that.
What was the name of the bar, Maria?
Uh I don't even know the name of it. All
I know is it's the cold beer and Polish.
Yeah. You used to play pool at 6?
Yes.
6 years old?
Yeah, dude.
That's a rough environment.
you, man, I remember one of my favorite
things when I worked with my when I
Jay won't let me say I was doing a
shift. When I went with my dad when he
worked at Dan's Liquors in Mill Valley,
one of my favorite things was turning on
the opening sign cuz when you're a kid,
it's just like simple stupid My
dad was like, "Hey, turn on the opening
sign." AND I'D BE LIKE, "WOO!" IT'S LIKE
LAUNCHING A SPACE YOU'RE LIKE, "KZZ."
It's just It's just opening the door for
a bunch of alcoholics. It's like 7:00 in
the morning and people are coming in and
now I'm at 35 like those people had
crazy problems.
I like that you guys are your your
father's uh child drinking buddies. You
realize it?
Yeah, that's what it is. Hey, I made my
own drinking buddy.
So you would go with your grandfather
and was this always after church or was
this daily?
This was daily.
Yeah.
You go to church daily
and then over to a bar.
church. No, no, not to church. There was
always an excuse to go to church. Really
we were at the bar.
Oh, he called it church.
grandfather passed away were people like
he was a deeply religious man and you
had to be like no, no, no, he's a booze
bag.
Guy went to mass every day.
Yeah.
Yep, pretty much, yeah. All of his quote
unquote church friends came to visit
during his funeral.
Dude, that's so funny.
Praise praise the Lord. I miss him so
much.
Bunch of bunch of guys in priest collars
with gin blossoms and just fat noses.
Bunch of fat Polish noses and they're
like
The Lord is a good man. The Lord give
us, the Lord take it away. Cuz they're
in Chicago, too. So they're just
hammered. They go, "This guy loved God
the way my ex-wife loves
It's a lot.
God bless.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Real talk right now.
Real talk, dog.
Is that called a gin blossom, the
bulbous nose?
Yeah.
Is it really?
Swear to God.
Brand new information to me.
Yeah, it's called a gin blossom.
I didn't know the name I didn't know the
name of the gin blossoms. What's the
name of the name for that?
Yeah, it's what it's like whenever you
see someone with a
Oh, I know, the old cha-cha-cha nose.
I just realized I had it just from
listening to the caller that I've gone
to two bar memorials. One for like a
friend that died and one for my
grandfather's sister. Like way different
generations. I'm like, "Oh, are bar
memorials not like
Uh one of the
the norm we do?"
Dude, one of the this is a
morbid aspect.
a yokel if your local bar has a
memorial.
Not local, but like the bar that they
hung out at. That's where everybody
went.
You're a legend.
Bar vigil.
Yeah, bar vigil. Oh, man.
There was a seat right there. Everyday
drinking alcohols.
Dude, so there was This is one of my
darkest memories of my dad dying. Was
like when I went to visit my dad when he
had like It was Thanksgiving of '97. He
died December 12th. So, he died like 2
weeks later. When I saw him dude, this
was I was 14. This was so awkward. One
of his bar friends or whatever, she came
over dressed like a sexy nurse. And my
dad's just at death's door step. But,
it's like that white trash bar mentality
doesn't understand the the weight of
this of the situation. So, she comes in
like, "Hey Gary."
I'm just
I'm sitting there like, Yeah, what? I'm
looking at my Aunt Karen like, "What's
up?" My Aunt Karen's like, "I don't
know what this is." But, she's
like, "I I
can help you feel better." Dude,
everybody was weirded out. It was one of
the
It was one of the weirdest My dad was
even like,
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Cuz he's not drinking now, you know?
He's like,
Mhm.
He's dying, but he's he's sober. And
he's like, "All right. Stop. Stop.
Stop."
Stop worrying here.
God
She came with the It was so
awkward.
to make little Gary feel better.
Dude, it was so It was almost like It
almost had that energy where you're
like, "Lady, leave."
"My family's here." He goes,
He goes, "This is my son."
I watched him all day. You're all pieces
of
Here's Here's a little chip off your
block, are you?
I'm like, "I don't know."
Say hello to Danny for me.
He's like grabbing my cheeks.
Yeah, you're a long way from Colorado.
It's a long way.
I'm like, "Please stop grabbing me."
Did you smell my fart from before?
Sorry, Dan. Sorry. Is the lip
hanging out?
Um Maria, thanks for the call.
Thank you. Longtime listener.
Hell yeah. Crackle, crackle. Thank you
so much. Marcus Silva says I was my
dad's bartender while we drove through
the Sequoia mountain roads. He would
hand me his empty
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, dude.
You're reloading the gun.
Yeah.
Like, oh, everybody doesn't have
alcoholic parents?
Yeah.
What's weird is when you have alcoholic
parents, you don't realize that there's
a kids that don't.
No, you're right.
Because alcoholics hang out with
alcoholics, and those are the kids that
you become friends with.
Yeah, I have Aunt Vicky, Uncle Cracker,
Uncle Chuck, Aunt Becky. These are all
my parents' friends.
Uncle Chuck is And Jay, that's why I say
that
I drunk with Tommy. I drunk with Tommy.
You know what Tommy is? He's a drunk.
But I've always said
that's why I say that that Jewish people
are the chosen ones. You guys handle
alcoholism.
You guys are top notch.
Uncle Mark was long, long time heroin
addict.
My dad
You either go big or nothing. I'm saying
Swedish garbage.
Swedish white trash, we're good at
getting cirrhosis young. We just do
different numbers.
What about the garbage Christine?
That's just That's beach trash. That's
different. Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
My parents have 60-year-old bottles of
liquor in their house that have never
been opened.
Never been opened, yeah.
My dad looks at me and points it out if
I if he sees me drinking a beer.
My friends used to laugh at how many My
friends used to laugh at how many empty
175s of Southern Comfort we had in our
recycling bin. When they walked out to
my garage, they'd be like
My friend Gary Barry was like, "Jesus,
soda?" And his dad was a liquor
distributor. And he's like, "Fucking
what is Trish and Joe doing?" I was
like, "I'll tell you this, they're
building a comedian."
What are they doing?
Recipe.
I need a recipe.
Uh let's take one more call before the
break here with Sal from Chicago. This
is pretty nutty.
Um
Sal, you there, buddy?
Crackle crackle.
Crackle crackle dude, you're on the
bonfire.
What's your bar kid story?
Well,
uh I might just want to preface this by
saying my dad wasn't much of a day
drinker. He didn't drink every day. He
never drank at home, but when he went
out to drink, he was more of your
classic binge type drinker and was
really
dis- What did he What did he disappear
for days?
No, he wouldn't Well, well, that did
happen a couple of times, but
uh not not that often. The The one time
though that I remember specifically when
I was probably like eight or nine and I
was uh my sister was babysitting me. My
mom was
I think she was at work. I can't
remember exactly. She wasn't home. And
my dad calls home from a police station.
He had got pulled over drunk driving
and convinces my sister, who's probably
16 at the time,
17 maybe, to go pick him up at the
police station.
Sick.
And then he he he bribed us with
Kentucky Fried Chicken to not tell my
mother.
That's so great. The KFC got you to
bury a DUI from your mom.
He goes, "Where did you She goes, "Well,
Mom, question, where did you get
chicken?" And you're like, Dad. Dad said
it's cool. Also, why does your dad smell
like swamp?
Uh did you ever Did you your mom ever
find out about that DUI?
No, I don't think so. I never told her.
I don't think my sister ever did.
That chicken was bond.
Yeah, dude. Your dad got you.
You You could never be a politician.
You'd be bought and paid for.
Chicken is bond.
Joining us from This is so awesome to
say. From Capital Wrestling, bringing
the new wave of pro wrestling to
Brooklyn. Join them on June 24th, it's
your boy's birthday, at St. Patrick's
Catholic Academy for a live
international television taping
featuring the biggest stars of Capital.
And one of the stars of Capital
Wrestling is here right now,
Zack Amico.
Thank you for having me, boys. Isn't it
fun that I weaseled my way into a
wrestling company?
I love it, dude. I love it. As a
as a wrestling mark, I totally love it.
It's my vision quest.
Yeah, you did it, dude. You got in What
I had to do was dress like a retired pro
wrestler
Yeah,
you just call everyone brother.
Yeah.
And then they're like, "Hey, this guy's
a wrestler."
Is it the most Is it your like most
dream job happening when you're doing
it?
It's
huge. Like since I'm
breaking Before I can remember, I
watched wrestling with my grandfather
and told him I wanted to be Mr.
Perfect's tag team partner.
Yeah, really?
Cuz I wanted to be a bad guy.
Yeah, so you always want to be heel.
I
Owen Hart was my favorite wrestler.
Great.
I've wanted to be a sneaky, shitty
person.
Now
Nobody has ever said that ever before.
Ever, but that's
Owen Hart was my favorite wrestler of
all time.
Yeah, well, you know.
He's like
I'm not speaking ill of the dead, I'm
just saying.
No, I was I was trying to think of a way
I could say that he was my favorite when
he fell, but I couldn't come up with it
cuz I'm still kind of high from earlier.
What I was going to say to you Yeah,
hey, he was high for a little bit.
What I was going to say to you is
there.
Yeah, it finally I knew Zach had to have
the jam it unlocked. He just had
to jam it. What is Breaking Kayfabe?
What is your role in Capital Wrestling?
Breaking Kayfabe, I uh now I'm one of
the producers of their television
product.
That's awesome.
Uh and we just This week my match aired
last week on UK television and we beat
MLW and Impact.
There you go.
So we are now the We were the highest
rated non-WWE wrestling product in the
UK.
So and this is Capital Wrestling in
Brooklyn.
Yeah, we're going to do our tapings June
24th in Brooklyn.
Uh just signed the Notorious 187
Homicide.
Okay, yeah, wow.
And uh a lot of really great guys. It's
uh we're stepping it up. We're going to
Nashville in August. Uh we're we're
making this a full touring production.
That's awesome, man.
Yeah, you're base It's kind of cool,
man, watching through the internet that
the the wrestling territories, they're
not really necessarily territories, but
things are popping up now. With Capital
Wrestling, you got AEW in another major
form. There's other like New Japan is
more accessible than it used to be.
No, we're all we're all nipping at the
bosses' heels.
Yeah, it's pretty fun, man. As a
wrestling fan, it's like kind of cool
cuz you just get to see a bunch of stuff
that maybe because of the internet that
you would I like New Japan, you'd have
to you used to go get tapes and like do
the all this weird to watch it. And
now it's on Axis Television and you can
get it online.
Do you think maybe
being an adult who still likes wrestling
has something to do with having
alcoholic parents in your life?
I don't know, man. Maybe that made it.
Is that what Is that what makes
wrestling fans?
Is that what makes wrestling fans?
Alcoholic parents?
your dad picks the bottle over you, you
have to like a guy who has orange skin
and yellow and red.
Or just that's what was left on when
somebody fell asleep.
You go, I guess Sting's my new uncle.
I'm going to watch this guy.
Hey Stinger. Hey Uncle Stinger.
Before Zach, before you were on, we
brought up the subject of I told Jay a
story of going to a bar called
Caledonia's in Aurora with my dad.
Like he was regaling me with a story of
what we were talking
a good memory. It was like a fun memory
of going to this bar. Uh do you have any
of those kind of memories?
No, because my dad got sober before I
was born.
Okay.
But my my dad is like vehemently
anti-alcohol.
Okay, yeah. So he's one of those where
he's like
Like still talks at meetings 35 years
deep.
That's great though.
But when he left my mom, she became a
bartender out of spite.
Really?
Which
you got to really respect that level
Dude, serving
of pettiness?
Serving the thing that your husband
hates?
Uh it was uh she he left and she went to
bartending school within like 3 months.
That's great.
That's great. And to this day bartender
at an Olive Garden in New Jersey.
Yeah.
Slinging them. Slinging those
white wines.
at Olive Garden?
Carlo Rossi.
Uh when I growing up, quite a bit.
But she worked there a long time?
She worked there from when I was in high
school on and I always thought we got
free Olive Garden.
Yeah.
And then I found out when I was a
grown-up, she just got like 20% off.
that much and you were ordering like it
was free?
No, no, no. That's just what we had so
much and I was like, "Oh, you just
didn't like cooking."
That's it. Yeah, she didn't even get
that much of a discount.
Yeah, she I don't know it's here. You're
here.
And I mean like the salad and
breadsticks at family dinner. Like
people
I was going to say what she I was going
to say what she would bring the salad
and breadsticks. OH, JANET IS HERE WITH
THE breadsticks and the salad. I hope
but this one does have an end to it.
Would she plate the food? Would she
plate the food pretending it was like
from her?
No, she would just
bring it. Like bring like the giant
salad.
With like an Olive Garden bag.
I'll tell you this man, if your mom and
my mom were friends, I would definitely
stick in to make sure your mom got an
invite so some of those breadsticks were
coming along.
Tell you what, breadsticks and salad all
day long.
All day long at Olive Garden.
I could go eat a whole meal of just
breadsticks and salads.
And when the salad's done and you just
use the bread to soak up all that goofy
dressing they put on there.
Never ending pasta month in my house.
Was the greatest month of their life.
Night My mom would come home like she
worked at a coal mine.
Really?
Somebody got eight plates today and
tipped me a dollar. Like just
My mother died of tomato lung.
Empty pasta month, she was just
breathing in tomatoes.
imagine if you worked if you lived in a
household where mom came home from
shrimp fest at Red Lobster?
A black home?
So what I'm saying is a black home.
Man, dude, that's got to that's
hilarious. You knew that month was bad.
You're like it's coming.
Oh yeah, it was it was
Unlimited pasta month. Man, people go
there and just post up, right?
For days, like crazy.
I was so excited about Olive Garden the
other day on the show and then you
really do realize this garbage.
That's what I said to him. I said it to
him and he goes, "No, I do like Olive
Garden's food." I go, "They're right now
trying to get rid of their inventory so
much they're giving you two meals for
then less than what one should cost."
Still looks good.
That can't be good
I'll go eat it right now.
quality food.
I do my my mom's a trooper though. She
will defend it. Every time somebody
makes fun of Olive Garden, she'll be
like, "Zachary, there's a three-hour
wait
at Olive Garden. Indian people love it."
And I'm like, "That's all you need to
know cuz it's Italian food.
Yeah, it was Olive Garden, Italian.
We'll go. It's uh Well, I went there a
lot growing up though, man, for sure.
Olive Garden?
Yeah.
Lot of Olive Garden. I went to
Applebee's a lot.
I did not go to Applebee's a lot. My
franchises we went to a lot
were I mean, we did plenty of fast food.
Fuddruckers, we did Fuddruckers.
Fuddruckers, Red Robin.
Yeah, I worked at a Red Robin. So, I was
I was I was on the ground floor of that
one.
seen a Red Robin.
Those boots I love Red Robin. I'll do a
Blue Ribbon Burger with an egg
on it.
Try to think of franchises. We didn't go
to a lot of franchise places.
Bennigan's.
I love a Bennigan's.
Houlihan's.
I love a good Bennigan's, man.
Houlihan's we always
Fridays sometimes.
What's that?
Houlihan's was trash.
Sure, yeah, absolutely. They're all
ground round.
Applebee's Applebee's on Iliff is still
going. Iliff and 225.
Ground round is basically an Applebee's.
Yeah. Look at the Blue Ribbon Burger. I
ate that so much.
From where?
Blue It's Red Robin.
What's that?
Red Robin's like They're all the same
kind of not good. Just eat it.
garage kid. This is delicious.
I like when you fetal alcohol
kids turn on each other.
I love when you two babies get mad at
each other.
I like when you you
banana heads start clunking.
Yeah, so you so you you didn't grow up
in you didn't have to go to bars or
whatever. I told Jay this and then we
opened it up for the callers.
844-266-3999 if you were a bar kid and
spent a lot of time in a bar with your
parents. We got a bunch.
Yeah.
Someone's uh grandmother died from
heroin.
That's I mean,
A kid had to drive his dad home 30 miles
every night at 12 years old.
That's bring that up.
All right.
What? Just take this call real quick.
Michael in Texas.
Yeah, cuz Michael in buys all the way.
Michael, I just want to say hello, but
real quick, what a Texas story. That's a
country song that you drove your
dad 30 miles home.
Yeah.
Why 30 miles, Michael? Why did he drink
so far away?
Well, we lived in at the time we lived
in New Mexico in uh Capitan.
It's about uh 30 40 mi away from
Ruidoso. So, there wasn't a bar in
Capitan.
The bar was in Ruidoso.
Jesus.
Man, you think he would have just moved
before he taught a 12-year-old to drive.
Was it a What kind of car was it?
It was a one of those Chevy Astro vans.
Yeah. Oh, man. I drove an Astro van from
Denver to Tucson.
That is great.
of leg room, though.
Great van. It's a big box.
you're sitting up. It's It's very uh
yeah.
It's the mega bus of vans.
Plenty Plenty of room in between the two
front seats for a big cooler of beer.
Oh my god.
keep ripping while you were driving at
12.
Yeah. Uh
well,
he would go to a place called Farley's
every night and hand
The names are always so great.
He would hand me about, I don't know, a
pocket full of quarters and send me into
the arcade.
Dude, arcades were the babysitters of so
many children of alcoholics. You get
that I know how to manipulate a
dollar in in a quarter machine one of
those machines that turns into quarters.
I could play it with my eyes closed. If
I you you could wad up a $5 bill, I'd
make that son of a work on that
machine.
love that the the thing that's funny is
my mom. I used to go to work with my mom
a lot.
Yeah, you were Yeah, you were a mall
kid.
I was a store kid. Well, there was never
a mall. It was like an But I like you
our our shitty like little mall that
wasn't like, you know, like It wasn't
like a shopping mall.
But you're doing sword fights with the
king.
place them all the day at an arcade and
then there was one next to a movie
theater and arcade, but it was always
like some retail or tuxedo rental place.
Yeah.
It was like you guys had the parents you
had to go to work and then even their
work was like alcoholicy also. It's like
It's like, "Well, we go to the liquor
store and I play with guys and look at
porn and then my dad takes me to a bar
afterwards."
On one from a long day at the liquor
store. You're just constantly surrounded
by Captain Morgan.
Yeah. He looked over me. The same Oh,
you mean Saint Morgan?
And you're going to school constantly.
Michael, did you go to school often with
your dad's free booze t-shirts?
First off, Jay.
It wasn't free booze shirt.
uh he drank he drank uh Milwaukee's Best
and I had probably about six t-shirts.
Yeah, dude.
Also, Jay's trying to besmirch the cool
Joe Camel shirt that I wore to school.
Holy
I slept in a Joe Camel shirt until I was
like 12 years old.
Monster.
Slept in it.
This was back when like Mortal Kombat
just came out on
I know, cuz that's what I was just
saying that. That was the arcade I went
to. It was Street Fighter II and Mortal
Kombat.
are lucky to be a little younger. I
would have had to watch my dad get drunk
while I played Pit-Fighter.
That's that's pretty gay. I was over at
the Neo Geo ripping it on World Heroes.
Yeah, that's way better. My video games
were worse. I would have to Karate
Champ.
And just go
just 16-bit jumps over.
So, when you would drive, did you at
what point did you become comfortable
driving the van home?
Uh probably about the sixth or seventh
time.
And then about
the same grade, by the way.
By the tenth time
grade. I think it was though. Wasn't it
the same?
By the By the tenth time you can drive
it one hand and have a cigarette hanging
out the window.
It's a candy cigarette.
That'd be great.
God damn it, Dad. Hold it down. Learn
how to hold it down. I don't know where
my child voice is Jacob voice. I
apologize, Jacob. I don't mean
Real nice, dude. Way to treat Jacob.
When you Did you ever get pulled Did you
ever get pulled over?
No, uh but what he would do is
we'd leave the bar and go across the
street to the liquor store
and he'd get a 30-pack of Milwaukee's
Best
for the trip home.
Jesus.
And uh
Well, he was one of those
you know, during the day like
treated us like and then when he
got drunk it was nothing but
you know, how much he loved you and
Dad, you just hung over all You just
hung over all day.
I love it. He goes, "You kids ain't
just like your mom." And then he gets
hammered and goes,
"You want to drive?"
Dude, what a better way that's such
There's so many alcoholic the children
There's so many children of alcoholics
that are hearing this that had the flip
where their dad was like really nice
during the day and then he'd get drunk
and just be a monster. That's almost in
a weird way. I don't know if I'm saying
that's I that might be preferable.
Am I crazy that DJ
Ludacris grabbed it like that? Would
your dad better drunk?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he was to a T.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was a way He was more fun to have.
I thought that's what he said. I thought
he said when his dad was drunk is when
it was all like, "I love you guys, man.
I'm sorry I act like an asshole."
And when we'd have a tall boy Budweiser
cans for breakfast.
Hell yeah.
Oh, what? Breakfast of champions?
better with eggs.
All right.
You want to have some Texas toast and a
tall boy?
I still say PBR is the breakfast beer.
Yeah, PBR is a real snap it open cuz
your wife got killed by a gang
member.
Not even cold.
It's That's death wish breakfast.
Yeah.
That's like ch- And like you've been off
the Yeah, it's warm. It was on the
window sill.
Over a short stack you barely eat it and
you put a cigarette out into it.
And then you put your gun around your
shoulders. You show your shoulder strap.
Another goddamn day living. Cleaning up
this cesspool known as Los Angeles.
Um
How old were you when you started
smoking cigarettes, Michael?
Do what?
How old were you when you started
smoking cigarettes?
Uh that was my brother that taught me
that when I was about 14.
Yeah, all right. I was going to give it
12 to 14 age range.
That's the wheelhouse. Were you still
playing with toys?
Booze babies always start smoking around
the same age
cuz you watch it.
Well, my my dad would also when we he'd
want to take a road trip to the lake
he'd have us drive the van and he'd take
his Harley.
Jeez, what a weirdo.
motorcycle.
Did your dad get drunk and
in the shoulder
he pulled up in the shoulder of the road
when he wanted beer and we'd hand him
one get going down the highway at
So you guys were just a moving cooler?
You guys are just
Yep.
You guys are just a You guys are
just a mobile beer stand?
This will be the first time I ask this
question to not a girl at a bar. So,
how'd your dad die?
Yeah.
Uh he's
He actually got got a disease when he
was in prison.
Oh man, holy
Well, I do That is That was just such a
alley-oop to yourself dunk of sad, where
I was like, "Oh man, he's going to say
yes." And he goes, "He got a disease in
prison." And you're like, "How do you
just go up and up again?"
Yeah.
A disease? Prison?
Jesus, it was like the slam dunk
contest.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. HE WAS
LIKE, "OH MY GOD, HE THREW IT OFF THE
BACKBOARD AND WENT THROUGH HIS LEGS."
LET'S SEE IF IT GETS SADDER. If the
disease is AIDS, then it's even sadder.
Oh no, what is it? What disease did he
get?
Uh some nerve disease that uh
nervous system disease that attaches
your nervous system. You start twitching
a lot, and then you
In prison? What was he What was he
in prison for?
Uh non-payment of child support.
But I let him drive. BUT I LET HIM
DRIVE, THOUGH.
I GAVE HIM WAIT, SO YOUR MOM took him
Your mom took him to prison?
Put him in Oh, the actually the Texas
the US Marshals, when they
in instituted that deadbeat dad crap,
they put a uh
a
a federal warrant out for him in
What year was that?
Why would your dad the marshal?
No, I want to know if my dad died I want
to know if my dad I want to know if my
dad died before the law.
You can marshal and TAKE YOUR DAD.
1998? IT WAS 1998? I'M SORRY, that's
crazy. That My dad died IN DECEMBER OF
'97. GARY hit a buzzer beater.
Yeah, dude, that's crazy. Your dad would
My dad would have gone to prison.
For not paying? Dude, my dad didn't pay
child support once in 9 years.
He just not pay child support until '98.
LIKE LIKE NOT THAT AGO. HE JUST HAD
BASTARD children and leave them off to
fend for themselves. No problem.
Crazy. So, how long was your dad in
prison for when he got the disease? Like
how long was he going to serve?
Well, he got 5 years
and served like three three of it.
And then he did he did he pass away in
prison?
No, he got out and
struggled for probably 10 or 15 years
and then then then did it.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
dude.
His stupid ass His stupid ass got caught
cuz he ran to Mexico when he got heard
the warrant was out.
He really didn't want to take care of
you.
Dude, your dad is straight up a Merle
Haggard song.
Yeah, Hey Joe, huh?
He's like running down in Texas got the
bar driving the van.
Ripping some Milwaukee Beast.
I'll tell you this though, dude. Your
dad is definitely a Gary.
Your dad's a first round draft pick for
the Gary's.
Your dad's riding his Harley in heaven
right now where they can't enforce this
child support law.
He's drinking and driving up in the big
up in the clouds.
He's driving his own Astro van.
He's got his own cooler beer.
His stupid ass got caught coming across
the Mexico border with a loaded loaded
pistol. That's how the marshals caught
him.
He shot a man in Reno just to watch him
die.
I mean, it really just keeps getting
worse. He's like, "Well, I was
kidnapped. I was with them. I was
I'm a child of rape.
Yes, he had my took my mother.
So, you Oh, man.
The positive The positive thing about it
is you you learn what not to do.
Yeah, I mean, exactly.
a GG Allin song.
Yeah.
And now you just let your kid sit in the
passenger seat while you drive drunk.
But but but more to the point, what
brought this all up was when you drove
that van, do you look back fondly at
that? Is like, "Oh, yeah, that was a a
thing my dad and I did.
Yeah, that was the
that was probably the most fun I ever
had with my dad because
Yeah, you guys
over like I told you, he was just a just
a
Yeah.
He gets her damaged.
We're all damaged.
You know girls in this room is not
You know there's a lot of girls who are
troubled enjoy dick.
Oh, God bless them.
It's just the problem surrounded uh
Hey.
Hey, double oh
you mean double down Evans over there?
She's got both. She's a bar kid.
Depends what day you ask.
Uh thank you so much for the call
Michael. That was a
yeah. Thanks for calling in, man.
We'll get a We'll get a GoFundMe up for
your therapy.
And I was born in an Astro van and my
father ran to Mexico.
Kelly got
For what?
What's happening? Oh, son of a
All right, you know what? It actually
did work out.
All right, got you.
I'm Batman.
That's the closest I've ever felt to
Batman.
I didn't see it coming at all. This
looks like a bad uh
Wait, now you do me. Let me be the guy a
little.
That was
We're going to do everything we can do
to not be welcome in this building.
Let's make this elevator porn.
Dan
You're going to have 36 floors to pop.
I'm going to need you to work quick. I'm
going to need you to get yourself in a
head space to finish quick.
Are we going to corner?
Yeah, work yourself up.
Can we go to
And the male talent is here. Now.
Where's Barkley?
Where is Barkley? I ask that a lot.
Come on, guys.
And normally there'll be male talent
here, but now today Andy's going to be
our male talent.
You know, you just hold it like this.
This is
holding it like this.
Hello, live from the elevator. It's Dan
Soder for Bonfire News. I just pulled
out my bag of weed when I went for my
work badge in front of the security
guard.
You think she's going to tell on you?
She didn't No, she didn't talk to me.
I don't like this.
I'd be mad if she was like,
Is this a security alarm or are all
these cops?
Keep that down. You know popo come.
Is there hair on
Take this plate off your head.
Becky, are you still mad at me?
No.
Two for two.
You've already gotten over it?
Why were you mad at me? Two for two.
She said I was cold and not friendly.
Well, you do have a wall.
Tear is an icy nut to crack.
I'll tell you what, you just got in
Dan's head for the rest of the day with
that line. That was a walk-off home run.
Becky, that was a walk-off home run.
Yeah.
You think he's not going to think about
that later when he's eating cereal
alone?
I don't eat
I don't eat cereal on Wednesdays.
That's so great. For his sake, he goes,
"No."
She goes, "No, I was kidding, but you do
put up a wall. Anyway, I'm going to be
over here."
Good luck to you anyways. Good luck
relating to anyone outside of your inner
circle.
All right, bye.
You think you're friends with Dig This
Video? Then share it with them and tell
them to rate and review. And you know,
make us feel good about ourselves.
You tell a friend, they tell two
friends. Yeah, it's a pyramid scheme of
a radio show.
It becomes a whole thing. I got some
Cutco knives also if you're interested.
Ooh, I got Spyderco, so come
come to me if you want the real one.